This catalog is buffer catalog for "Baidu Player".
Saving files in this catalog can reduce buffer time when you watch videos and allow you to watch videos you recently watched when "Baidu Player" doesn't connect with the Internet.
If you don't need these buffer files or don't have enough disc room, yoou can delete them manually.
This will not affect normal operation of the software.
Note:Before deleting them, please exit "Baidu Player" or "Baidup2pservice"program to avoid failure of deleting because of reading and writing of content by the software.
